{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947474906","data":{"timestamp":" 946947474906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947482113","data":{"timestamp":" 946947482113"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947487187","data":{"timestamp":" 946947487187"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947495976","data":{"timestamp":" 946947495976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947502923","data":{"timestamp":" 946947502923"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947507722","data":{"timestamp":" 946947507722"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947513027","data":{"timestamp":" 946947513027"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947519109","data":{"timestamp":" 946947519109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947523662","data":{"timestamp":" 946947523662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947529417","data":{"timestamp":" 946947529417"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947534816","data":{"timestamp":" 946947534816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947541543","data":{"timestamp":" 946947541543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947552545","data":{"timestamp":" 946947552545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 473b16f5-83ee-4ffe-8a6d-eea03cc152e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947563862","data":{"timestamp":" 946947563861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" va"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VA"," userResponse":" VA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947566943","data":{"timestamp":" 946947566942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" va"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947568551","data":{"timestamp":" 946947568550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ve"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VE"," userResponse":" VE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947571873","data":{"timestamp":" 946947571873"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ve"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947573414","data":{"timestamp":" 946947573414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VI"," userResponse":" VI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947576726","data":{"timestamp":" 946947576725"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947578322","data":{"timestamp":" 946947578321"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VO"," userResponse":" VO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947581291","data":{"timestamp":" 946947581291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947582864","data":{"timestamp":" 946947582864"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" VU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947585854","data":{"timestamp":" 946947585854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947587863","data":{"timestamp":" 946947587863"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947588023","data":{"timestamp":" 946947588023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 904d0e58-d030-4cbe-8a4b-ab1ee6caf853"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947598943","data":{"timestamp":" 946947598943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947608328","data":{"timestamp":" 946947608328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-13-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947616136","data":{"timestamp":" 946947616136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-15"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947623926","data":{"timestamp":" 946947623926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_11-5-7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947629093","data":{"timestamp":" 946947629093"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_16-10-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947635925","data":{"timestamp":" 946947635925"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_11-6-14"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947653697","data":{"timestamp":" 946947653697"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-6-15"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947657564","data":{"timestamp":" 946947657564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947663333","data":{"timestamp":" 946947663333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-6-14"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947672330","data":{"timestamp":" 946947672330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_8-3-7"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947679514","data":{"timestamp":" 946947679514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-15-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947686656","data":{"timestamp":" 946947686656"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947693343","data":{"timestamp":" 946947693341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 93ed5e1f-0a7d-4f74-984f-4769e1fedc9b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.decr.17"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-13"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947704034","data":{"timestamp":" 946947704034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" va"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947705062","data":{"timestamp":" 946947705062"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" va"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VA"," userResponse":" VA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947711045","data":{"timestamp":" 946947711045"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ve"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947712105","data":{"timestamp":" 946947712104"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ve"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VE"," userResponse":" VE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947716680","data":{"timestamp":" 946947716679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947717736","data":{"timestamp":" 946947717736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VI"," userResponse":" VI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947724730","data":{"timestamp":" 946947724730"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947725794","data":{"timestamp":" 946947725793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VO"," userResponse":" VO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947733398","data":{"timestamp":" 946947733398"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947734464","data":{"timestamp":" 946947734463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" VU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947737797","data":{"timestamp":" 946947737796"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947737938","data":{"timestamp":" 946947737938"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VU"," userResponse":" VU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947893361","data":{"timestamp":" 946947893359"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" e6206b06-d1cd-49dc-bc0d-37fecc13f578"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.va..vu.asc.lc.20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" vu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947893456","data":{"timestamp":" 946947893456"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 52604abd-9b7c-40cd-a95e-73adfeb9bf8b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_63"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naye alitaka kufa."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFA"," userResponse":" KUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947905643","data":{"timestamp":" 946947905643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947911734","data":{"timestamp":" 946947911734"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947916793","data":{"timestamp":" 946947916793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" ha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947922848","data":{"timestamp":" 946947922848"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947928214","data":{"timestamp":" 946947928214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947937170","data":{"timestamp":" 946947937170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947945424","data":{"timestamp":" 946947945424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947949630","data":{"timestamp":" 946947949630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947955636","data":{"timestamp":" 946947955635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947963181","data":{"timestamp":" 946947963181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947967899","data":{"timestamp":" 946947967899"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947973669","data":{"timestamp":" 946947973668"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c95f8398-6031-4e66-93c1-e94b6bdbd01a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947988276","data":{"timestamp":" 946947988276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946947994412","data":{"timestamp":" 946947994412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_4-6-14"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948002757","data":{"timestamp":" 946948002757"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_10-6-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948007676","data":{"timestamp":" 946948007675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948013088","data":{"timestamp":" 946948013088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-10-14"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948020553","data":{"timestamp":" 946948020553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_13-6-14"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948028489","data":{"timestamp":" 946948028489"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_10-13-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948034004","data":{"timestamp":" 946948034004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-16-13"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948039563","data":{"timestamp":" 946948039563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948045367","data":{"timestamp":" 946948045367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948057288","data":{"timestamp":" 946948057287"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_16-3-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948067011","data":{"timestamp":" 946948067011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948073662","data":{"timestamp":" 946948073662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 4ac75584-3df2-4790-b1d5-2447fbf0def6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-6-7"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948084596","data":{"timestamp":" 946948084596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948092169","data":{"timestamp":" 946948092169"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948096605","data":{"timestamp":" 946948096605"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948102342","data":{"timestamp":" 946948102341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948108155","data":{"timestamp":" 946948108154"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948112558","data":{"timestamp":" 946948112558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948118917","data":{"timestamp":" 946948118917"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948124542","data":{"timestamp":" 946948124542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948128851","data":{"timestamp":" 946948128851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948133016","data":{"timestamp":" 946948133016"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948138779","data":{"timestamp":" 946948138778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948189655","data":{"timestamp":" 946948189655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2ae6e5d1-8a2c-44bb-94a8-afba3620815b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948189727","data":{"timestamp":" 946948189727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 5a6f3d0f-f2c7-4728-959b-8223562c6ade"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliharakisha kurudi kijijini."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948200523","data":{"timestamp":" 946948200523"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_mta-go-do"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948205621","data":{"timestamp":" 946948205621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-mbu-fo"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948210214","data":{"timestamp":" 946948210214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-ngu-mgo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948214575","data":{"timestamp":" 946948214575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-ya-ngu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948218493","data":{"timestamp":" 946948218492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-go-fa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948224120","data":{"timestamp":" 946948224120"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_yu-go-ba"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948229509","data":{"timestamp":" 946948229508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-di-nyo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948233639","data":{"timestamp":" 946948233639"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-ba-za"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948238232","data":{"timestamp":" 946948238232"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-go-ri"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948243374","data":{"timestamp":" 946948243374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nyo-de-go"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948249151","data":{"timestamp":" 946948249147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nyo-de-go"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948288261","data":{"timestamp":" 946948288261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 804ea81f-f4b8-48b7-9ab1-d99dec264d51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.show.17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nyo-de-go"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948300552","data":{"timestamp":" 946948300552"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GA"," userResponse":" GA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948303742","data":{"timestamp":" 946948303741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948305306","data":{"timestamp":" 946948305306"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GE"," userResponse":" GE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948308577","data":{"timestamp":" 946948308576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ge"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948310153","data":{"timestamp":" 946948310153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GI"," userResponse":" GI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948313055","data":{"timestamp":" 946948313054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948314630","data":{"timestamp":" 946948314630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" go"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GO"," userResponse":" GO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948317474","data":{"timestamp":" 946948317473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" go"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948319134","data":{"timestamp":" 946948319133"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GU"," userResponse":" GU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948322103","data":{"timestamp":" 946948322102"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948324128","data":{"timestamp":" 946948324127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948324294","data":{"timestamp":" 946948324294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1ff316e9-4f98-47e4-a9c6-8e6468cb000d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ga..gu.asc.lc.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" gu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948333986","data":{"timestamp":" 946948333985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948334219","data":{"timestamp":" 946948334216"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948335196","data":{"timestamp":" 946948335196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948336485","data":{"timestamp":" 946948336484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948339372","data":{"timestamp":" 946948339371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948340237","data":{"timestamp":" 946948340236"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948340558","data":{"timestamp":" 946948340557"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948341804","data":{"timestamp":" 946948341803"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948345393","data":{"timestamp":" 946948345392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948346392","data":{"timestamp":" 946948346391"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948346651","data":{"timestamp":" 946948346651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948347608","data":{"timestamp":" 946948347606"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948350546","data":{"timestamp":" 946948350545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948351589","data":{"timestamp":" 946948351588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948352065","data":{"timestamp":" 946948352065"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948356642","data":{"timestamp":" 946948356640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948356731","data":{"timestamp":" 946948356731"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1b66f9f6-d394-4ca8-924b-6c46bd49f51e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_25"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948367814","data":{"timestamp":" 946948367814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-mke-nga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948374567","data":{"timestamp":" 946948374567"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_twe-ri-go"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948382970","data":{"timestamp":" 946948382970"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_bu-two-go"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948388381","data":{"timestamp":" 946948388381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nda-jo-go"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948392928","data":{"timestamp":" 946948392928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_mpa-nye-go"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948397433","data":{"timestamp":" 946948397433"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-mje"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948409223","data":{"timestamp":" 946948409223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_ze-go-mke"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948414250","data":{"timestamp":" 946948414250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_mji-ngu-go"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948418686","data":{"timestamp":" 946948418686"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-va-twa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948423302","data":{"timestamp":" 946948423302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nyo-kwe-go"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948429079","data":{"timestamp":" 946948429075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nyo-kwe-go"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948469142","data":{"timestamp":" 946948469142"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 522d34a2-a925-46b2-a800-3629a4984947"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_go..go.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_go_nyo-kwe-go"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948479390","data":{"timestamp":" 946948479390"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948483845","data":{"timestamp":" 946948483845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948489059","data":{"timestamp":" 946948489059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948493959","data":{"timestamp":" 946948493958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948499516","data":{"timestamp":" 946948499516"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948504072","data":{"timestamp":" 946948504072"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948509297","data":{"timestamp":" 946948509297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948513564","data":{"timestamp":" 946948513564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948518993","data":{"timestamp":" 946948518993"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948523492","data":{"timestamp":" 946948523492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948529287","data":{"timestamp":" 946948529283"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 2151b489-12c8-4ae0-9de7-76c58345c37c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948542105","data":{"timestamp":" 946948542105"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vo_vo-po-to"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vo"," userResponse":" vo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948552494","data":{"timestamp":" 946948552494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_go_go-lo-po"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948562191","data":{"timestamp":" 946948562190"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_li_li-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" li"," userResponse":" li"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948566423","data":{"timestamp":" 946948566423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fa_fa-ra-sa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fa"," userResponse":" fa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948575717","data":{"timestamp":" 946948575717"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_pu-ru-lu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948579846","data":{"timestamp":" 946948579846"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ri_ri-fi-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ri"," userResponse":" ri"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948584131","data":{"timestamp":" 946948584131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mo_mo-ko-ro"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mo"," userResponse":" mo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948590030","data":{"timestamp":" 946948590030"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bu_bu-zu-fu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bu"," userResponse":" bu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948594826","data":{"timestamp":" 946948594826"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-to-vo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948601070","data":{"timestamp":" 946948601069"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948606858","data":{"timestamp":" 946948606856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" c71cc288-7910-4910-937d-f2d554928b3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.48__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_me_le-me-re"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948675298","data":{"timestamp":" 946948675298"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948723286","data":{"timestamp":" 946948723285"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948772457","data":{"timestamp":" 946948772457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948777414","data":{"timestamp":" 946948777413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948779991","data":{"timestamp":" 946948779990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948840061","data":{"timestamp":" 946948840061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948842493","data":{"timestamp":" 946948842492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948890630","data":{"timestamp":" 946948890630"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948896875","data":{"timestamp":" 946948896875"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948899775","data":{"timestamp":" 946948899775"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948904322","data":{"timestamp":" 946948904322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948961468","data":{"timestamp":" 946948961468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948961555","data":{"timestamp":" 946948961555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 89adf716-83a1-4aa2-b519-4feaa20e2c4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_62"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliyafumba macho yangu nikinuia kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948983470","data":{"timestamp":" 946948983470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mta_ha_mzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948990079","data":{"timestamp":" 946948990079"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mlu_mka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946948996688","data":{"timestamp":" 946948996688"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ya_ha_chu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949003315","data":{"timestamp":" 946949003314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_ha_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949009944","data":{"timestamp":" 946949009944"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mzu_bwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949016590","data":{"timestamp":" 946949016589"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nju_mke_ha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949023254","data":{"timestamp":" 946949023254"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mpa_ha_mwo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949029913","data":{"timestamp":" 946949029913"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ki_ha_mmo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949036567","data":{"timestamp":" 946949036566"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbe_ha_twi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949043231","data":{"timestamp":" 946949043231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949056397","data":{"timestamp":" 946949056396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 1d60a2a6-8c1e-4235-a68d-b60fb4554873"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949079610","data":{"timestamp":" 946949079610"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mta_ha_mzi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949086253","data":{"timestamp":" 946949086252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mlu_mka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949093876","data":{"timestamp":" 946949093876"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mlu_mka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949104172","data":{"timestamp":" 946949104172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mlu_mka"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949110399","data":{"timestamp":" 946949110399"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ya_ha_chu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949117034","data":{"timestamp":" 946949117034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ku_ha_mno"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949123706","data":{"timestamp":" 946949123706"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_mzu_bwe"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949130354","data":{"timestamp":" 946949130354"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nju_mke_ha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949137830","data":{"timestamp":" 946949137830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_nju_mke_ha"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949144439","data":{"timestamp":" 946949144438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mpa_ha_mwo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949151067","data":{"timestamp":" 946949151067"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ki_ha_mmo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949157676","data":{"timestamp":" 946949157676"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mbe_ha_twi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949164320","data":{"timestamp":" 946949164319"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949173182","data":{"timestamp":" 946949173181"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:4..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.decr.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946949182266","data":{"timestamp":" 946949182266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000104_035737"," gameId":" 36a7d029-0704-47c0-bdad-e1e4e8cb1764"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ha..ha.noShow..7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_ha_nyi_we"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}